print("questions imported")
maths_question = [{'type': 'mcq',
                   'question': 'For some integer m, every odd integer is of the form, ',
                   'answer': 'd',
                   'options': '(A) m (B) m + 1 (C) 2m (D) 2m + 1'},

                  {'type': 'mcq',
                   'question': 'The pair of equations x + 2y – 5 = 0 and −3x – 6y + 15 = 0 have:',
                   'answer': 'c',
                   'options': 'A) A unique solution B) Exactly two solutions C) Infinitely many solutions D) No solution'},

                  {'type': 'true/false',
                   'question': 'The length of tangents drawn from an external point to a circle are equal',
                   'answer': 'true'},

                  {'type': 'true/false',
                   'question': 'The slope of a vertical line is undefined.',
                   'answer': 'true'},

                  {'type': 'one word',
                   'question': 'What is the median when it is given that mode and mean are 8 and 9 respectively.',
                   'answer': '8.67'},

                  {'type': 'one word',
                   'question': 'What is the range of the first 10 prime numbers ? (Statistics)',
                   'answer': '27'}]

sci_question = [{'type': 'mcq',
                 'question': 'What is known as the powerhouse of the cell ',
                 'answer': 'c',
                 'options': 'A) Ribosomes B) Nucleus C) Mitochondria D) Vacuole'},

                {'type': 'mcq',
                 'question': 'Fermi is a unit of',
                 'answer': 'a',
                 'options': 'A) Length B) Mass C) Time D) Electric Flux'},

                {'type': 'true/false',
                 'question': 'abc',
                 'answer': 'true'},

                {'type': 'true/false',
                 'question': 'abc',
                 'answer': 'false'},

                {'type': 'one word',
                 'question': 'abc',
                 'answer': 'xyz'},

                {'type': 'one word',
                 'question': 'abc',
                 'answer': 'xyz'}]

gk_question = [{'type': 'mcq',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'xyz',
                'options': 'A) opa B) opb C) D)'},

               {'type': 'mcq',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'xyz',
                'options': 'A) opa B) opb C) D)'},

               {'type': 'true/false',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'true'},

               {'type': 'true/false',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'false'},

               {'type': 'one word',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'xyz'},

               {'type': 'one word',
                'question': 'abc',
                'answer': 'xyz'}]
